# Nima Ferdousi

### **Front-end Developer**

nimalangariferdowsi1383@gmail.com



#### **SKILLS**

Html - Css

Javascript - Typescript

React - React native

Nextis - Redux

Webpack-Git

Scss-bootstrap-material

wordpress

Node is - Express is

Mongodb - Mysql Tailwind

#### Soft SKILLS

Leadership

Communication

Problem-solving

Time Management

Team-oriented

#### LANGUAGES

English (Advanced)

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **Azad University**

Studying for Bachelor Computer Engineering

#### **SUMMARY**

Experienced **almost for 5 years** worked in different companies and I've also had the incredible journey of founding and running my own web agency for a while(not doing it anymore) and been in participate in variety of projects in that journey I also learned tho how manage a project

**Freelance Projects**: You can find my former agency and projects that I have done as a freelancer in following <u>Link</u>

**Portfolio Projects**: You can find some of my portfolio projects with the source code in the following Link

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Sinansoft, USA — Frontend developer

#### OCT 2022 - PRESENT

I was a frontend developer in this company and coordinated in in different projects Like:

**.Univoip:** Contributed in creating a user-friendly website for UniVoIP, a telecom company. The site enables users to effortlessly utilize and Create VoIP numbers, improving communication options for individuals and businesses. Website

**.Centralive:** coordinated as frontend developer for website( client and admin dashboard) and mobile app of it, this project was about health study that some researches would assign some tasks to participants base on their oura rings data and collecting data Website

.Sinansoft: Recreated the website of company with nextis

**.Loanthem:**Developed an app and website that revolutionized the borrowing and lending experience. Users can easily navigate, make agreements, and set up contracts for hassle-free financial transactions developed with react for website and react native for app (APP:Loanthem)

**.Rally:**Contributed significantly to an app that simplifies the process of booking sports courts, hosting events, and connecting with players. Added user-friendly features to enhance the overall experience. developed with react for website and react native for app

Yemeksepeti , (Turkey) — Frontend developer

#### MAY 2021 - OCT 2022

Frontend developer in this company that was a food delivery company in in turkey I help in map sections real time process and app developed with react

Website

## Cloudtree/Cloud4agri,(ireland)—Frontend developer **JUNE 2019 - MAY 2021**

This was the first company that I worked with and I was added first as intern then full time I help them in their website and projects and added to a game project that was created with Html Css and javascript Game:word mastermind company website